Guide to the Fort Pitt Bridge Works, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1886-1949 AIS.1963.27
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Fort Pitt Bridge Works, Pittsburgh, Pa., Records
1886-1949
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Fort Pitt Bridge Works
AIS.1963.27
13.75 Linear Feet
The Fort Pitt Bridge Works was engaged in the construction of steel bridges and mill buildings, the production of structural steel work and reinforcing steel for road work and buildings, the pressing and welding heavy plate sections, and the engineering and manufacturing of combustion systems for industrial furnaces. This collection contains records regarding the organization and operation of the Fort Pitt Bridge Works including minutes, tax records, articles of incorporation, etc.
History
The Fort Pitt Bridge Works of Pittsburgh, Pa., was formed in May of 1896 by the merger of the Pittsburgh Architectural Iron Works with Straub and Bickle. The Pittsburgh Architectural Iron Works was operated by George Delenbacker and William and George Ebenhardt, who owned a small steel making plant in Cannonsburg, PA. Straub and Bickle was an engineering and contracting firm headed by Theodore Straub and H.R. Bickle. In 1930 the Fort Pitt Bridge Works purchased the Massillon Bridge and Structural Steel Works of Massillon, Ohio. On January 1, 1946 the Fort Pitt Bridge Works became a wholly-owned subsidiary by the Electric Welding Company.
The Fort Pitt Bridge Works provided steel for projects in Pittsburgh and across the nation. Nationally, the Fort Pitt Bridge Works contributed to projects such as the construction of the Lackawana Steel Company building in Buffalo, NY. The corporation also provided the steel used in the construction of the Jefferson Memorial in Washington, D.C. The Fort Pitt Bridge Works was also active in the war effort in both World War I and World War II. The Fort Pitt Bridge Works made a great many contributions locally including the construction of the Pennsylvania Turnpike and much of Pittsburgh's infrastructure. Many of Pittsburgh's bridges (the Sewickly Bridge, the McKees Rocks Bridge, Point Bridge, the 16th Street Bridge, the 31st Street Bridge, Smithfield Street Bridge, Bloomfield Bridge, California Avenue Bridge, Wilmot Street Bridge, and many of the bridges on the Penn-Lincoln Parkway) and Pittsburgh's steel frame buildings (the Sheraton Hotel, the Pittsburgh Press Building, Psychiatric Hospital, the Federal Building and the Syria Mosque) are the results of steel from the Fort Pitt Bridge Works.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection consists of the records of the Fort Pitt Bridge Works, known before 1930 as the Fort Pitt Bridge Works of Pittsburgh, PA, which was incorporated in 1896. In addition it contains the records of its predecessor, the Pittsburgh Architectural Iron Works, as well as the records from the Massillon Bridge and Structural Steel Works of Massillon, OH, which was purchased by Fort Pitt in 1930. There are also records from the Massillon Steel Erecting Company and the Flint Structural Steel Company, Massillon, OH, both of which were absorbed into the Fort Pitt Bridge Works. These records include documents pertaining to the company's incorporation, information regarding stockholders and the company stock, correspondence, news clippings and other printed matter covering the period from 1896 through 1946 when Fort Pitt was purchased by the Electric Welding Company.
Records on microfilm are identified by the following record group abbreviations:
Fort Pitt Bridge Works Records are identified as "FPBW" Massillon Bridge and Structural Steel Works of Massillon, Ohio are identified as "MBSSW" Pittsburgh Architectural Iron Works Records are identified as "PAIW"
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Donald Straub on December 5, 1963.
Previous Citation
Fort Pitt Bridge Works, Pittsburgh, Pa., Records 1886-1949, AIS.1963.27, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Industries -- Ohio -- Massillon; Corporation records; Iron industry and trade -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Industries -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Transportation; Steel industry and trade -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Business and Industry; Steel industry and trade -- Ohio -- Massillon; Iron industry and trade -- Ohio -- Massillon; Building, Iron and steel -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Bridges -- Design and construction; Flint Structural Steel Company (Massillon, Ohio); Fort Pitt Bridge Works; Massillon Bridge and Structural Steel Works; Massillon Steel Erecting Company; Pittsburgh Architectural Iron Works
- FPBW Historical Background, 1896-1949 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Volume 1)
- FPBW Letters Patent, 1896 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 2)
- FPBW Application for Incorporation, 1896 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 3)
- FPBW Charter, By-Laws, 1895-1906 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 4)
- FPBW Amendments to the By Laws, 1915 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 5)
- FPBW Correspondence Concerning Charter, By-Laws, 1915 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 6)
- FPBW Dissolution, 1941-1946 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 7)
- FPBW Plant Inventory, 1901 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 8)
- FPBW Properties, 1896-1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 9)
- FPBW Contracts, 1896-1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 10)
- FPBW Officer's Salaries, 1896-1927 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 11)
- FPBW Guaranty given to Carnegie Steel Co., 1899 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 12)
- FPBW Purchase of Property, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 13)
- FPBW Mortgage and Deed of Trust with Union National Bank, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 14)
- FPBW First Mortgage, Union National Bank, 1944 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 15)
- FPBW Appraisal, 1930-1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 16)
- FPBW Certified appraisal of properties, 1921 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 17)
- FPBW Bill of sale, F.P.B.W. of Pittsburgh, PA to F.P.B.W., 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 18)
- FPBW Name Change, 1930-1931, 1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 1, Folder 19)
- FPBW Certificate of Withdrawal, 1931-1933 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 19)
- FPBW Depreciated Summary Report, 1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 19a)
- FPBW First Annual Revision Report, November 16, 1922 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 19b)
- FPBW Second Annual Revision Report, 1923 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 19c)
- FPBW List of Bd. Names, Voting of Stock, 1904, 1908-1912, 1920-1923, 1925-1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 22)
- FPBW Waiver of Notice and Proxies, 1920-1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 23)
- FPBW Correspondence, 1902-1905 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 24)
- FPBW Legal Documents, 1903, 1921, 1925, 1933 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 25)
- FPBW List of Stockholders, 1894-1930, 1943-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 26)
- FPBW Notarized List of Stockholders, 1923-1924, 1926-1928, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 27)
- FPBW Legal Documents, 1926-1928, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 28)
- FPBW Correspondence, 1925, 1927-1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 2, Folder 29)
- FPBW Disbursement of tax refund payment, 1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 36)
- FPBW Stock Value after Company Name Change, 1932, 1940-1941, 1943, 1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 37)
- FPBW Increase in Capital Stock, $200,000-$400,000, 1902 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 38)
- FPBW Increase in Capital Stock, $400,000-$600,000, 1905 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 39)
- FPBW Increase in Capital Stock, $600,000-$800,000, 1907 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 40)
- FPBW Increase in Capital Stock, $800,000-$1,200,000, 1925 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 41)
- FPBW Correspondence on Increase in Capital Stock, 1902-1905 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 42)
- FPBW Correspondence on Increase in Capital Stock, 1924-1925 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 43)
- FPBW Legal Correspondence on changes stock value, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 44)
- FPBW Correspondence on the sale of stock, 1905, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 45)
- FPBW Report of capital stock, 1896-1899 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 46)
- FPBW Sale of stock to employees, correspondence on sale of stock, 1905-1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 47)
- FPBW Stock Dividend Reports, 1927 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 48)
- FPBW 5,000 unissued stock certificates to issued, 1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 49)
- FPBW Correspondence of Special Stockholders Meeting, 1927, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 50)
- FPBW Legal documents, waiver of meeting, 1927, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 51)
- FPBW Stock certificates, Republic Bank Note Company, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 52)
- FPBW List of Bondholders, 1932 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 53)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Returns and Reports, 1909-1912 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 72)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Returns and Reports, 1913-1914 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 73)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Returns and Reports, 1915-1916 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 3, Folder 74)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Returns and Reports, 1917-1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 75)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Returns and Reports, 1919-1920 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 76)
- FPBW Booklets from Federal Government, 1919-1920 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 77)
- FPBW Booklets from Federal Government, 1931-1938 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 78)
- FPBW Booklets from Federal Government, 1939-1946 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 79)
- FPBW Federal Income Tax Correspondence, 1910-1920, 1931-1949 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 80)
- FPBW Petition for Resettlement of Taxes, 1932 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 81)
- FPBW Audit Information, 1930-1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 4, Folder 82)
- FPBW Federal Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1917-1919 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 83)
- FPBW Federal Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1922-1926 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 84)
- FPBW Federal Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1934-1938 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 85)
- FPBW Federal Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1940-1944 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 86)
- FPBW Capital Stock Correspondence, 1917-1947 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 87)
- FPBW General Information, 1916 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 88)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Capital Stock Reports, 1931-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 89)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Income Tax Reports, 1935-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 90)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Corporate loans tax report, 1936-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 91)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Domestic bonus report, 1941-1946 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 92)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Transmittal Slips, 1939-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 93)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Settlement Corporate Income Tax, 1941-1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 94)
- FPBW Commonwealth of PA Correspondence on Taxes, 1936-1952 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 5, Folder 95)
- FPBW General Information on Pennsylvania Taxes, 1936-1940 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 6, Folder 96)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Agreement to build in Youngstown OH, 1916 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 6, Folder 107)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contract to build crane runway for A.M. Byers, 1916 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 108)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contract plans for various projects, 1916 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 109)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contract proposals, proposals, orders, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 110)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contract proposals, orders, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 111)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contracts, general correspondence, 1919 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 112)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Correspondence, orders, proposals and blueprints, 1917 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 113)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Contracts, correspondence, summaries of job completed, 1917 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 7, Folder 114)
- FPBW Respondent Exhibit: Correspondence, orders, summaries of completed jobs, 1917 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 115)
- FPBW Stipulation Exhibits: Corporation Waiver, 1921-1922 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 116)
- FPBW Stipulation Exhibits: F.P.B.W. and the U.S. Military Signal Officer, 1917 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 117)
- FPBW Stipulation Exhibits: F.P.B.W. and the Bureau of Aircraft Production, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 118)
- FPBW Stipulation Exhibits: Officer of the Director of Aircraft Production, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 119)
- FPBW Stipulation Exhibits: Director of the Military Aeronautics Board, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 120)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Agreements with the US Military Signal Division, 121, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 121)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Correspondence with U.S. War Department, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 122)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Materials correspondence, and specifications for jobs, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 123)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Assessment of Taxes, 1909-1919 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 124)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Correspondence from Treasury Department concerning excise tax, 1924 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 125)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Property analysis from the Treasury Department, 1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 126)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Minute book of jobs, 1896-1901 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 127)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Three Blueprints from Mill Buildings for St. Louis Screw Co., 1914 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 128)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Blueprints for Peoria and Pekin Union Ry. Co., 1917 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 129)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Blueprints for Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Co. for proposed single track crossing over North East River, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 130)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Estimates, 1914 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 131)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Blueprints for Youngstown OH Iron-Steel Co. open-hearth building, 1914 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 132)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Location of Jobs, Blueprints, 1915-1927 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 133)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Canonsburg photos, Patterned Warehouse, 1929 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 134)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Blueprints, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 135)
- FPBW Petitioner's Exhibits: Blueprints, 1918 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 8, Folder 136)
- FPBW Misc. Court Case Material, 1931-1941 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 137)
- FPBW Plants in Pittsburgh PA and Canonsburg PA, 1903, 1908 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 138)
- FPBW Press Clippings, 1894, 1907, 1909, 1927, 1930, 1942-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 139)
- FPBW Annual Dinner Program Menu, 1912, 1914, 1916, 1919 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 140)
- FPBW The Greater Pittsburgh Exposition Society, 1935-1936 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 141)
- FPBW Constitution and By-Laws of the Bridge Builders Society, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 141a)
- FPBW In Memoriam: Joseph Dean Brown, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 141b)
- PAIW Vouchers, 1896 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 145)
- MBSSW Articles of Incorporation, 1909 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 9, Folder 146)
- MBSSW Blueprints, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 169)
- MBSSW Sale agreement documents between Massillon and the National Defense Plan Corp., 1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 170)
- MBSSW Liquidation of Massillon, 1941 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 171)
- MBSSW Transfer of deeds between Massillon and the Defense Plant Corporation, 1942-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 172)
- MBSSW List of interested buyers of Massillon, 1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 173)
- MBSSW Sale or transfer of equipment, 1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 10, Folder 174)
- MBSSW Accountant firms appraisal of Massillon: American Appraisal Company, Coats and Buchard Co., 1941-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 11, Folder 175)
- MBSSW Correspondence Concerning the appraisal of Massillon, 1941-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 11, Folder 176)
- MBSSW U.S. Justice Department Material concerning the appraisal of Massillon property for use as a war production facility, 1942-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 11, Folder 177)
- MBSSW Correspondence concerning the sale of Massillon, 1942-1943 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 11, Folder 178)
- MBSSW Telegraph Correspondence concerning the sale of Massillon to various branches of the US Government, 1940-1942 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 11, Folder 180)
- FPBW Cashbook, May 1896-April 1900 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 63)
- FPBW Certified appraisal of properties, 1921 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 16a)
- FPBW Certificate of Withdrawal, 1931-1933 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 19)
- FPBW Depreciated Summary Report, 1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 19a)
- FPBW First Annual Revision Report, November 16, 1922 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 19b)
- FPBW Second Annual Revision Report, 1923 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 12, Folder 19c)
- FPBW Minute Book, April 1896-April 29, 1913 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 13, Folder 20)
- FPBW Minute Book, February 14, 1913-January 29, 1921 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 13, Folder 21)
- FPBW Certificate of stock books, Vol. 3 #1-250, October 11, 1929-June 24, 1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 14, Folder 33)
- FPBW Stock Ledger, 1896-1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 14, Folder 30)
- FPBW Stock Certificate Record Book, 1929-1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 14, Folder 31)
- FPBW Certificate of stock books, Vol. 2, January 25-December 7, 1928 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 15, Folder 32)
- FPBW Checkbook, October 19, 1931-May 6, 1946 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 15, Folder 58)
- FPBW Checkbook, December 17, 1930-October 1, 1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 15, Folder 57)
- FPBW General Ledgers, 1896-1902 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 16, Folder 54)
- FPBW General Ledgers, 1906-1919 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 17, Folder 55)
- FPBW General Ledgers, 1896-1900 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 17, Folder 56)
- FPBW Checkbook, October 10, 1941-October 18, 1946 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 18, Folder 59)
- FPBW Checkbook, November 26, 1943, May 10, 1945 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 18, Folder 60)
- FPBW Checkbook, May 10, 1945, January 12 1949 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 18, Folder 61)
- FPBW Cashbook, May 1900-Febraury 1903 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 18, Folder 62)
- FPBW Cashbook, March 1903-June 1907 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 19, Folder 64)
- FPBW Cashbook, July 1907-October 1911 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 20, Folder 65)
- FPBW Cashbook, November 1911-October 1915 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 21, Folder 66)
- FPBW Cashbook, November 1915-May 1920 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 22, Folder 67)
- FPBW Cashbook, January 1913-July 1922 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 23, Folder 68)
- FPBW Journal, May 1896-December 1905 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 24, Folder 69)
- FPBW Accounts payable ledger, 1900-1907 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 25, Folder 70)
- FPBW Contract ledger; contracts, #1-500, May 1896-1901 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 26, Folder 71)
- PAIW Bond, no date (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 27, Folder 142)
- PAIW Stockholders Ledger, 1894-1895 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 27, Folder 143)
- MBSSW Minute Books, 1901-1912, 1923-1930 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 27, Folder 147)
- MBSSW Preferred Stockholders, 1912-1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 28, Folder 149)
- MBSSW Stock Ledger, 1912-1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 28, Folder 150-153)
- MBSSW Stock registers stockholders ledger, 1912-1931 (Microfilm-cabinet 1, Reel 28, Folder 148)